[{"question": " great.  great! just give me a sec to change film.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": "  okay, i know i&#146;m not supposed to know, but i do. and i&#146;m so excited for you!", "answer": " what? what&#146;s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " monica&#146;s pregnant!", "answer": " oh my god! is that why you guys had to get married?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " guys! i&#146;m not pregnant.", "answer": " ah.  slow swimmers?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " what?! what do you mean? you-you-you&#146;re not pregnant?", "answer": " you didn&#146;t tell anybody i was did you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " now why don&#146;t we get a shot of just monica and the bloody soldier.", "answer": "  oh, about that. joey, you have to change before the party.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " i can&#146;t! i-i don&#146;t have any other clothes here.", "answer": " find some! please! anything that doesn&#146;t say i-i died tragically in france.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " well then why don&#146;t we see the bride and the groom and the bride&#146;s maids.", "answer": " okay.  hey mon, why did you tell the guys you weren&#146;t pregnant?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " because i&#146;m not.", "answer": " we found your test in the trash, if you&#146;re not pregnant&#151;&#151;it&#146;s because i am.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " what?! what are you talking about?", "answer": " what are you talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yes, i&#133;i am with child.  and i didn&#146;t want to say anything because it&#146;s your day; i didn&#146;t want to steal your thunder.", "answer": " wait a minute! so you told people i was pregnant?!  does this look like a conversation that i want to remember?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " who&#146;s the father?", "answer": " yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " i can&#146;t say.", "answer": " why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " why not?", "answer": " i can&#146;t say because he&#146;s famous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " phoebe, come on, you have to tell us.", "answer": " okay, okay. it&#146;s james brolin. james brolin is the father of my baby.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " as in barbara streisand&#146;s husband james brolin?", "answer": " what?! well he never said that to me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " why don&#146;t we have monica step away and we&#146;ll get chandler and the bride&#146;s maids.", "answer": " how about just the bride&#146;s maids?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " y&#146;know i am the groom right? i was told it was kinda big deal.", "answer": " it is.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " oh, thank you for doing that. i just can&#146;t deal with this just quite yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " so instead you told me monica was pregnant.", "answer": " you said that she was, i just didn&#146;t disagree with you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " sneaky.", "answer": " oh yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " smile ladies.", "answer": " oh!  oh by the way?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " uh-hmm.", "answer": " james brolin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " oh, i know. i could only think of two names, him and ed begley jr. and then i remembered he&#146;s gay.", "answer": " ed begley jr. is not gay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " before we go out there i&#146;ve got a present for ya.", "answer": " honey, i&#146;m going to put my hand in your pocket!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " no?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i&#146;ve been taking dancing lessons.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah, the last six weeks. i wanted this to be a moment you will never forget.", "answer": " oh that is so sweet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " so? would you care to join me in our first dance as husband and wife?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " what&#146;s the matter?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know, it&#146;s these new shoes, they&#146;re all slippery.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " well, are you going to be able to do this?", "answer": " not well.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " so, are you ready to talk about it?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " now?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " okay, we&#146;ll talk about something else then.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " who&#146;s the father?!", "answer": " ugh! look honey y&#146;know what? i haven&#146;t told him yet, so until i do i don&#146;t think i should tell anybody else.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yeah. that&#146;s fine. that&#146;s fair. is it tag?", "answer": " phoebe!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay, i&#146;m sorry. i&#146;ll stop.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " is it ross? it&#146;s ross isn&#146;t it&#151;oh my god, it&#146;s joey!", "answer": " honey, stop it! i am not going to tell you until i tell him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  oh sweet lord.", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry! okay? i went down to the gift shop and it&#146;s either this or a bathrobe! look, what&#146;s more important, the way i&#146;m dressed or me being with you on your special day?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " hi. i&#146;m uh, i&#146;m ross. i don&#146;t, i don&#146;t believe we&#146;ve met. i&#146;m monica&#146;s older brother.", "answer": " oh hi, i&#146;m, i&#146;m mona from her restaurant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " oh! hello uh, mona from her restaurant.   mona, wow what a, what a beautiful name.", "answer": " you think so? i&#146;ve always kinda hated it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " aw come on, mona lisa?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " mona umm&#133;clickclocken. the famous botanist? huh? oh no she&#146;s uh&#151;well she&#146;s dead now. no, supposedly she was once quite the hottie of the plant world.", "answer": " really?! well see? i never knew about her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " linda clickclocken.  so what uh, what-what table are you at?  oh, uh me too.", "answer": " oh good. now there&#146;ll be someone there who likes my name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " chandler darling! look, my date has finally arrived. i&#146;d like you to meet dennis phillips.", "answer": " congratulations.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " dennis is a dear old friend and a fantastic lover.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " bravo dennis thanks for pleasing my mother so.", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m so sorry i missed the ceremony, i was stuck at auditions.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " oh yes, dennis is directing a new broadway show.", "answer": " i don&#146;t believe we&#146;ve met, joey tribbiani.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " dennis phillips", "answer": " wow, i&#146;ve admired your work for years. you-you&#146;ve done some really amazing stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " wow dennis phillips! that&#146;s great! how did you guys meet?", "answer": " well, it&#146;s a funny story.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " hey! uh, i thought, i thought you were at table six.", "answer": " no, nine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " chandler. will you see if your mom can give my resume to dennis phillips? &#145;cause if i can get in a broadway show then i would&#146;ve done it all, film, television, and theater. the only think left would be radio, and that&#146;s just for ugly people.", "answer": " what size shoes do you wear?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " uh, eleven, eleven and a half.", "answer": " great, because my shoes are giving me a little problem on the dance floor, can i borrow the boots from your costume?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " uh, i don&#146;t even really know where i left those. sorry.", "answer": "  those aren&#146;t eleven and a half.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " can you believe phoebe got pregnant?!", "answer": " oh y&#146;know what honey? let&#146;s not talk about that right now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " this is so huge.", "answer": " sure, but come on, as big as your wedding?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " of course not nothing is. between me and you&#133;", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " &#133;in this day and age how dumb do you have to be to get pregnant?", "answer": " hey! y&#146;know, sometimes you can do everything right, everyone can wear everything they&#146;re supposed to wear, and one of those little guys just gets through!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " how?", "answer": " i don&#146;t know! maybe they have tools.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " well i-i talked to and uh, she&#146;s definitely going to have this baby. y&#146;know, she said she was gonna raise it on her own.", "answer": " well, maybe that&#146;s, maybe that&#146;s really brave.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " maybe. i just hope she realizes how hard it&#146;s gonna be.", "answer": " maybe she hasn&#146;t really thought it through that well.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well, there&#146;s a lot to think about. i mean, how is she, how is she going to handle this financially? how is she going to juggle work? does she realize she&#146;s not going to have a date again for the next eighteen years?", "answer": "  i don&#146;t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " are you okay?", "answer": " uh-hmm. i&#146;m just thinking about phoebe; poor knocked up phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " champagne?", "answer": " oh yes! thank you very much!  oh that&#146;s-that&#146;s actually how the french drink it.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " well, i just got off the phone with my lover, james brolin&#133;", "answer": " oh really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " yes, and apparently he is married to some singer, but he said he would leave her for me. and i said, &quot;james, james brolin, are you sure?&quot; james brolin said&#133;", "answer": "  rachel&#146;s really the one who&#146;s pregnant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  what?!  why bother?", "answer": " how do you feel?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i don&#146;t know. i don&#146;t know how i feel. this is all happening so fast. i have to make all these decisions that i don&#146;t want to make.  somebody just take this away from me!!", "answer": " calm down. maybe you&#146;re not pregnant.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " when i got pregnant with the triplets, i took that test like three times just to make sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " yes! maybe it&#146;s a false positive. are you sure you peed on the stick right?", "answer": " how many ways are there to do that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " i&#146;m-i&#146;m just saying, don&#146;t freak out until you&#146;re a hundred percent sure.", "answer": " all right, i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll take it again when i get home.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " you-you gotta take it now. come on, do it as a present to me.", "answer": " okay. thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " i&#146;ll run out and get you one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " oh, you guys are so great.", "answer": " oh, wait a minute! who&#146;s is the father?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " oh no, she won&#146;t tell us.", "answer": " oh, come on it&#146;s my wedding! that can be my present.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " wh&#151;hey, i just gave you peeing on a stick.", "answer": " see? this is why you register.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " umm, would you like to dance?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " sure.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " oh great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " dr. geller?", "answer": " i wasn&#146;t farting!  uh, a little game from our table.  yes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " dr. geller, will you dance with me?", "answer": " oh umm, well uh, maybe-maybe later. right now, i&#146;m about to dance with this lady.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " ohhhh!", "answer": " uh, unless! unless, uh this lady wouldn&#146;t mind letting you go first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " i&#146;d be happy to.  you are very sweet.", "answer": " yes i-i am. in fact umm hey, why don&#146;t we try it my special way? you can dance on my feet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " sure!", "answer": " yeah? hop on.  is the pretty lady looking?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " uh-huh.", "answer": " keep dancing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " and the world will never know.", "answer": " hey! did you talk to dennis about me yet?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " yes, i told him how talented you were. i told him all about days of our lives.", "answer": " no-no! no! no! you don&#146;t tell a broadway guy that! now he just thinks i&#146;m a soap actor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " but you&#146;re not just a soap actor. you are a soap actor with freakishly tiny feet.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": " no-no, thank you miranda.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " melinda!", "answer": " all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " how cute was that?", "answer": " oh-oh, were you, were you watching?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " can i go next?", "answer": " what? of course you can! hop on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " i am so gonna score.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " thank you.", "answer": "  that was very nice ashley.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " can we do it again?", "answer": " no-no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i&#146;m next!", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " uh, that&#146;s okay. you can dance with her first.", "answer": " oh, you-you sure?  okay.  okay. so what&#146;s uh, what&#146;s your name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " gert!", "answer": " that&#146;s, that&#146;s pretty.  whoa! whoa! whoa! what are you doing there gert?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " dancing on your feet! like the other girls did it.", "answer": " okay.  hop on gert.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " why aren&#146;t you moving your feet?", "answer": " i&#146;m trying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " faster! you&#146;re not going fast enough!", "answer": " maybe i should stand on your feet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " so did you uh, happen to catch my toast up there?", "answer": " oh my god, that was for my benefit?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " well, i&#146;d like to think there was something for everyone. look, i know you&#146;re casting for this new show&#133;", "answer": " look umm joey, i-i don&#146;t think you&#146;re quite right for this project.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " oh, see that&#146;s where you&#146;re wrong. whatever it is i can do it. and if didn&#146;t see it up there, just-just try me.", "answer": " it&#146;s an all chinese cast. can you be chinese?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " hey, are you ready to get back on the dance floor?", "answer": " did it turn into sand?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": "  no. no, i won&#146;t. do you know why i took all those lessons? see, for the first time i didn&#146;t want to be embarrassed to be seen on the dance floor with some clumsy idiot.", "answer": " oh sweetie, you can never embarrass me.  okay, you can easily embarrass me. but come on, it doesn&#146;t matter. all right? i married you! so i want to dance on my wedding night with my husband. come on.  just try not to move your feet at all.  there you go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " chandler, i&#146;m gonna have you arrested.", "answer": " why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " how much longer?", "answer": " 30 seconds.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " 30 seconds, okay.", "answer": "  did i miss it?  rachel, i-i want you to know that, if it&#146;s positive, we&#146;re gonna&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " oh wait! y&#146;know what? i can&#146;t, i can&#146;t look at it. i can&#146;t. somebody else tell me, somebody tell me.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " umm, it&#146;s negative.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " it&#146;s negative.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " oh. oh. well there you go. whew!  that is&#151;that&#146;s great&#151;that is really great-great news.  y&#146;know &#145;cause the whole not being ready and kinda the financial aspects, all that. whew. wow, this is so just the way it was supposed to be.  god.", "answer": " well&#133; well, great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " thanks.  god this is so stupid!  how could i be upset over something i never had? it&#146;s negative?", "answer": " no, it&#146;s positive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " it&#146;s-it&#146;s not negative, it&#146;s positive.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " are you sure?", "answer": " well yeah, i lied before.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " oh god&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " now you know how you really feel about it.", "answer": " oh-oh, that&#146;s a risky little game!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " are you really gonna do this?", "answer": " yeah. i&#146;m gonna have a baby. i&#146;m gonna have a baby. i&#146;m gonna have a baby!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " with who?", "answer": " ah, it&#146;s still not the time. dedicated to the people of new york city", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " i just didn&#146;t see the fast song coming.", "answer": " shh. shh. don&#146;t try to talk, we&#146;ll get you up to your room, we&#146;ll soak your feet, you&#146;ll be okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " oh, thank you.", "answer": " that is so sweet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " no, i mean it. there are so few genuinely nice guys out there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " tell me about it, i feel like i&#146;m holding down the fort all by myself.", "answer": " it&#146;s joey right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " wait a minute! no! i&#146;m the nice one! i&#146;m the one who danced with the kids all night! how&#133;how small are your feet?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s8/ep1.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}]